Guide to the Richard Pollay Acme Advertising Collection, 1850s-2006 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series 28: Miscellaneous Items, 1896-2002 and undated
  - 100-28-150. Acme Auto Paint & Supply Corp. Lighter, undated (Box 34)
    Metal Zippo style lighter. Red engraved lettering. Acme Auto Paint & Supply Corp. --Phone DI 2-0497. Used condition.
  - 100-28-151. Acme Foundry & Machine Company. Lighter, undated (Box 34)
    Metal Zippo style lighter. Red and black engraved lettering. The Acme Foundry & Machine Company Blackwell, Okla. Used condition.
  - 100-28-152. Acme Venetian Blind Company. Lighter, undated (Box 34)
    Metal lighter. Red with white lettering. Acme Venetian Blind Company--C. B. Peters Venetian Blind Company. Used condition.
  - 100-28-153. Masons Acme Lodge. 50th Anniversary Mini Trowel, 1939 (Box 34)
    Miniature mason's trowel. Engraved text reads: 50th Anniversary 1889-1939 ACME LODGE 554 Newark, Ohio. Also engraved is the Masons' logo. Good condition.
  - 100-28-154. Acme Motors Inc. Ashtray, 1976 (Box 34)
    Brown glass with white lettering. American Bicentennial themed ashtray. Acme Motors Inc. Kittanning, Penn.--1776-1976.
  - 100-28-155. Acme Markets, Inc. Novelty license plate, undated (Box 34)
    Novelty license plate featuring Acme Markets name and logo. Material is metal. White blue and red in color. As new condition.
  - 100-28-156. Acme. Nebraska novelty license plate Acme, undated (Box 34)
    Novelty Nebraska license plate. License plate spells ACME.
  - 100-28-157. Acme Chain Corporation. Acme Chain BMX racing number plate, 1984 (Box 34)
    Plastic licence plate style BMX number plate. Large black numbering: 51. Two small stickers read: 1984 Acme Chain. Acme Chain appears to be the sponsor of a racing event.
  - 100-28-158. Acme Products Inc. Fenda Hugga, undated (Box 34)
    Vinyl car fender protector. Intended for use by mechanics and people working on cars. Another Fine Acme Product--Fenda Hugga. Faded and aged condition.
  - 100-28-159. Acme Bicycle Repair. Framed item, undated (Box 34)
    Wood picture frame with home-made (folk art) 3-D design inside. Materials are wood, metal, and paint. Miniature bicycle made of metal wire with painted text Acme Bicycle Repair--All American Bicycles.
  - 100-28-160. Acme cobbler's box, undated (Box 34)
    Wood open topped box. Black lettering on side: Acme Cobbler's Outfit--For General--Boot, Shoe, Tinware, and Harness Repairing.
  - 100-28-161. Acme Cotton Products Company. First Aid Kit #50, 1966 (Box 34)
    Blue metal box with white lettering. First Aid Kit #50--Acme Cotton Products Company, Inc. Box is full of Acme brand first aid supplies. Some light surface rust on box. Contents in disarray.
  - 100-28-162. Acme Dunnage & Service Company. Bag, undated (Box 34)
    Novelty bag intended to hold two wine/liquor bottles. The bag resembles a golf bag. Brown and beige vinyl. Small gold lettering.
  - 100-28-163. Acme Tires. Banner, undated (Box 35)
    Large fabric wall hanging promoting Acme Tires. Red, black, and white lettering on white and red background. STOP! Get Our Prices Before You Buy!--Acme Mil-Master Tires. Very soiled and stained.
  - [Image only] 100-28-164. Acme Foundry, Inc. Lighter, undated (Box 35)
    Silver color metal Zippo lighter. Engraved and painted logo and lettering. Acme Foundry Inc. Coffeyville, KS.
  - 100-28-165. Acme Wringers, Ltd. Single clamp wringer, undated (Box 38)